MCKENNA POUWER

346-367-9078, mckenna.pouwer@gmail.com

LinkedIn Profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mckenna-pouwer/

Skills Summary

Passionate Trainer for volunteer missionaries with experience in practicing curriculum ideation/design. Experience in problem solving and iterating ideas. I hope to use design thinking in my future careers and education. Strong leader in the classroom and enthusiastic about helping people thrive. Enjoy innovating and collaborating within teams.

Skills

- Ability to Work in A team.
- Problem Solving
- Leadership
- Public Speaking
- Media Production

- Curriculum Ideation/Design
- Communication
- Some knowledge of Adobe Creative Cloud and Canva.

Education

Public Health/Minors in Business and Design Thinking

Emphasis in Health Promotion for Public Health. Exploring careers in business that include design thinking. Coursework includes practicing the design thinking process, instructional design, program planning, and media production for the BYU planetarium. I've participated in extracurricular activities including intramurals for frisbee and cross country. Also played in BYU's symphony for three semesters.

Experience

Charlie Academy

Volunteer 07/2023 to Current

- Build ideas and solutions for the academy in team settings.
- Involves research and gathering information on how to meet the needs of the Academy's customers/audience.

Utah Community Credit Union

Marketing Orientation Intern

05/2023 to Current

- Assist the Marketing team with analyzing and creating content for UCCU's website.
- Educating students at UVU during Orientations about UCCU's plus card.
- Involves communication skills, marketing products to students, teamwork with other interns, and good work ethic.

Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints - MTC

Tour Guide 08/2022 to Current

- Lead groups of 1-20+ people on tours of the Missionary Training Center in Provo, UT.
- Tours are in person and virtual.
- Requires skills in public speaking, knowledge of the campus, communication with other tour guides and visitors, and quickly handling issue to promote positive experiences.
- Involves helping with technology that is related to the tour (gimbles, mics, zoom).

Workshop Trainer

01/2022 to Current

- Train groups of 1-20+ volunteers to enhance their skills, while also developing public speaking and class management skills
- Identify qualified applicants through rating sessions to simplify the hiring process for supervisors.
- Train groups of young adult volunteers by facilitating workshops focus on fostering improved teaching and study skills.

English Teacher

05/2021 to 12/2021

- Teaching position where training is given to missionaries preparing to leave for their assigned cities and areas across the world.
- The training includes leading group discussions, demonstration, and practices, and working with other teachers on lesson plans.
- Involves skills of communication, presentation, coaching, and creativity.

Brigham Young University

Teaching Assistant

01/2022 to 4/2022

- Assisted with the Astronomy 127 class.
- Worked 1-2 times a week running telescopes.
- This included setting up telescopes with fellow peers, monitoring the telescope deck, and helping students complete class projects.

- Also learned beginner skills in working the university's planetarium, which included some coding experience.

Odd Jobs

Private Nanny 10/2016 to 04/2017

- Watched over two children once a week for about 2-3 hours.
- Kept the occupied through games and media.
- Required skills of communication, interpersonal skills, and resilience.

Hobbies

- Outdoor enthusiast
- Trail running
- Painting
- Astrophotography
- Music